Guide to the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Records, 1868-1991 bulk (1981-1990)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Office Files Series, 1972-1990, undated (bulk 1983-1988) (Box 9)
  - Program development committee: Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Proposal writing, undated (Box 11)
  - Public speaking, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Questionnaire development: (Box 11)
    - 1982-1983, undated (Box 11)
    - Roane/Calhoun survey, undated (Box 11)
    - Southern West Virginia survey, undated (Box 11)
  - Recordkeeping, undated (Box 11)
  - Reports: (Box 11)
    - 1985 (Box 11)
    - Annual reports from the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
    - Wealth in the United States, 1986 (Box 11)
  - School exhibit, undated (Box 11)
  - Sexual harassment: (Box 11)
    - 1977-1982, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Clippings, 1981-1982, undated (Box 11)
  - Southern Appalachian Leadership Training: (Box 11)
    - Training design: (Box 11)
      - Leadership vs. managers, 1983 (Box 11)
      - Lobbying, 1976-1985 (Box 11)
      - Writing legislators, undated (Box 11)
    - Workshop: Summary and evaluation, undated (Box 11)
  - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: (Box 11)
    - Ads in other organizations' ad books/anniversary issues, etc., 1987-1989 (Box 11)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1981-1990 (Box 11)
    - Board meeting minutes, Articles of Incorporation, Bylaws, 1981, Nov.-1985, Oct., (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Brochure, 1985, undated (Box 11)
    - Bylaws: (Box 11)
      - 1984-1990 (Box 11)
      - Corrections, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    - Information packet, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - Job descriptions: (Box 11)
      - 1985-1987, undated (Box 11)
      - Ford intern, undated (Box 11)
    - Newsletter policy and plans, 1983-1986 (Box 11)
    - Non-profit status, 1982-1988 (Box 11)
    - Organizational chart, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Organizational summary, undated (Box 11)
    - Orientation packet, 1987-1989, (3 folders) (Box 11)
    - Programs, public relations, 1982-1984 (Box 12)
    - Publicity, press, 1985-1987 (Box 12)
    - Staff members, 1986, undated (Box 12)
    - Stationery: Logos, business card proofs, etc., undated (Box 12)
    - Steering Committee: (Box 12)
      - 1985-1988 (Box 12)
      - Meeting notes and Articles of Incorporation, 1985, Oct.-1987, June (Box 12)
    - Support letters, 1985-1990 (Box 12)
    - Travel arrangements, 1985-1987 (Box 12)
    - Vendor and business contracts (names and addresses), 1989 (Box 12)
  - Staff recruitment: (Box 12)
    - Advertisings and mailings, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Job announcements, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Title IX vocational education information, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Tourism: Articles and notes, 1971-1988 (Box 12)
  - Trip reports, 1983-1989, (4 folders) (Box 12)
  - Unions, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Venture proposal for Martha's Place, undated (Box 12)
  - Women in unions, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Work plans, 1983-1989, (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Worker ownership, 1981-1983 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous: (Box 12)
    - 1983-1988, (3 folders) (Box 12)
    - Additions and corrections to newsletter mailing list/subscriptions, 1986-1988 (Box 12)
    - Clippings, 1982-1991, (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Donations and subscriptions, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous: (Box 13)
    - Listing: Periodicals, position papers, newsletters, catalogs, 1987 (Box 13)
    - National survey to review progress on 1977 national plan of action for women, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Newsletter corrections, deletions, additions, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Open house invitation, undated (Box 13)
    - Outside purchase orders, correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 13)
    - Payroll, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Publication orders to be filled, 1988-1990 (Box 13)
    - Speech class notes, undated (Box 13)
- Correspondence Series, 1981-1990, undated (bulk 1983-1987) (Box 13)
  Typewritten and handwritten letters, memoranda, and postcards. Arranged chronologically by incoming and outgoing mail. See addition to this series at end of container list.
  - Incoming, 1981-1984, undated, (3 folders) (Box 13)
  - Outgoing, 1983-1985, (13 folders) (Box 13)
  - Incoming, 1985, undated, (9 folders) (Box 14)
  - Outgoing, 1986, Jan.-Nov., (9 folders) (Box 14)
  - Incoming, 1986, (13 folders) (Box 15)
  - Outgoing, 1987, Jan.-Aug., (5 folders) (Box 15)
  - Incoming, 1987, (12 folders) (Box 16)
  - Outgoing, 1987, Sept.-1988, Apr., (6 folders) (Box 16)
  - Incoming, 1988, (9 folders) (Box 17)
  - Outgoing, 1988, May-1989, June, (11 folders) (Box 17)
  - Incoming, 1989, Jan.-1990, Sept., undated, (7 folders) (Box 18)
  - Outgoing, 1989, July-1990, Sept., (10 folders) (Box 18)
- Financial Papers Series, 1969-1991, undated (bulk 1981-1989) (Box 18)
  Financial reports, audits, and account books. Includes letters, reports, and budgets relating to a variety of funding agencies that supported the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition. Arranged into chrolonogical and alphabetical subseries. See addition to this series at the end of container list.
  - Chronological Subseries (Box 18)
    - 1980, Apr.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 18)
    - 1981, Jan.-1983, Mar., (18 folders) (Box 19)
    - 1983, Apr.-1984, June, (14 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1984, July-1985, Apr., (14 folders) (Box 21)
    - 1985, May-1986, May, (16 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1986, June-1987, July, (17 folders) (Box 23)
    - 1987, Aug.-1988, Oct., (18 folders) (Box 24)
    - 1988, Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - 1988-1989,Financial statistics, (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - 1988-1989,General ledger, (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - 1989-1990, Jan., (11 folders) (Box 25)
    - 1990, Mar.-Sept. (Box 26)
  - Alphabetical Subseries (Box 26)
    - Audits, 1983-1987, Sept., (6 folders) (Box 26)
    - Bank deposits, 1987, Dec.-1989, Aug. (Box 26)
    - Bank statements, 1988, Oct.-1989 (Box 26)
    - Banks: (Box 26)
      - Central Appalachian People's Federal Credit Union, 1986-1990, Apr. (Box 26)
      - The Cumberland Bank, 1985, Sept.-1988, Mar. (Box 26)
      - First Security Bank, 1982, Feb.-1990, Feb. (Box 26)
    - Bookkeeping records, 1980, Jan.-1984, Oct., (4 folders) (Box 26)
    - Budgets, 1982, Oct.-1989, (9 folders) (Box 26)
    - Cancelled checks, ca. 1988, Oct.-1989, Mar. (Box 26)
    - Cancelled checks, ca. 1989, Apr.-Nov. (Box 27)
    - Check stubs, 1983, Jan. 31-1989, July, (4 folders) (Box 27)
    - Financial statements, 1983-1987, (4 folders) (Box 27)
    - Funding Files: (Box 27)
      - Anonymous, 1984 (Box 27)
      - Agape Foundation, 1984 (Box 27)
      - Appalachian Community Fund, 1987 (Box 27)
      - Aspen Ford Foundation, 1986-1990, (2 folders) (Box 27)
      - Babcock, Mary Reynolds Foundation, 1985-1990 (Box 27)
      - Beatrice Foundation, undated (Box 27)
      - Beazley Foundation, 1984 (Box 27)
      - Bingham, William Foundation, 1984 (Box 27)
      - Campaign for Human Development, 1986, undated (Box 28)
      - Dayton, Alida and Mark Charitable Lead Trust, 1984-1986 (Box 28)
      - Donations, 1985-1986 (Box 28)
      - Eastman (Restaurant Employees Association of Lexington, Ky.), 1983 (Box 28)
      - Episcopal Church Center, 1983-1989 (Box 28)
      - Field Foundation, 1982-1986, undated (Box 28)
      - Ford Foundation, 1982-1990, (4 folders) (Box 28)
      - Funds for Southern Communities, 1984 (Box 28)
      - Funding Exchange (LD), 1983-1990, undated (Box 28)
      - Gerson Fund, 1984 (Box 28)
      - Greater Cincinnati Foundation, undated (Box 28)
      - Gund Foundation, 1983-1985, (2 folders) (Box 28)
      - Hilton, Conrad Foundation, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Jewish Fund for Justice, 1984 (Box 28)
      - Joint Foundation Support, 1984 (Box 28)
      - Joyce Foundation, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Kentucky Foundation for Women, 1985-1990 (Box 28)
      - Knight Foundation, 1987 (Box 28)
      - Knoxville Support Group for Women Construction Workers, 1982-1987, undated (Box 28)
      - Levi Strauss Foundation, 1982-1990, (2 folders) (Box 28)
      - MacArthur, J. Roberick Foundation, 1985 (Box 28)
      - MacArthur, John D. and Catherine T. Foundation, 1988-1990 (Box 28)
      - Methodists Call to Prayer Program, 1985-1986 (Box 28)
      - Metropolitan Foundation of Atlanta, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Ms. Foundation, 1982-1990, undated (Box 28)
      - New World Foundation, 1984-1990, (2 folders) (Box 28)
      - Norman Foundation, 1983-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 28)
      - Open Meadows, 1989 (Box 28)
      - Pallottine Center for Apostolic Causes, 1984 (Box 28)
      - Pettus-Crowe Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 28)
      - Playboy Foundation, 1983 (Box 28)
      - Poverello Fund, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Presbyterian Committee on the Self-Development of People, 1990 (Box 28)
      - Revson, Charles Foundation, 1990 (Box 28)
      - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc., 1977 (Box 28)
      - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1982-1987 (Box 28)
      - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1988-1990 (Box 29)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 29)
      - Sachem Fund, 1986 (Box 29)
      - Sisters of Loretto, 1984 (Box 29)
      - Sisters of Mercy, 1986 (Box 29)
      - Skaggs Foundation, 1985, undated (Box 29)
      - United Church of Christ Hunger Action Fund, 1987 (Box 29)
      - United Methodist Church, 1983-1985 (Box 29)
      - United Methodist women, 1985 (Box 29)
      - United Presbyterian Church, U.S.A., 1983 (Box 29)
      - Veatch Program (North Shore Unitarian Universalist), 1983-1990, undated (Box 29)
      - Whitney, John Hay Foundation: (Box 29)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 29)
        - Expenses, 1980-1983, undated (Box 29)
      - Windom Fiduciary, 1984 (Box 29)
      - Women of Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1990 (Box 29)
      - Women's Opportunity Giving Fund, 1979-1986, undated (Box 29)
      - Youth Project, 1984 (Box 29)
    - Funding Files: Miscellaneous: (Box 29)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 29)
      - Current funders, undated (Box 29)
      - Funding sources, 1987-1988, undated (Box 29)
      - Future funding prospects, 1987-1989, undated (Box 29)
      - Grants, 1979-1984 (Box 29)
      - History, 1979-1990, undated (Box 29)
    - Funding, new proposals, renewals, etc.: (Box 29)
      - Church funding sources, 1987, Aug.-1988, Feb., undated, (2 folders) (Box 29)
      - Mott, Charles Stewart, Foundation, 1987 (Box 29)
      - Prospects, 1990-1991, undated (Box 29)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Funding sources: General: (Box 29)
      - Fellowships, 1985, Aug.-1986, Apr., undated (Box 29)
      - Research funding sources, 1983-1986, Apr., undated (Box 29)
      - Responsive philanthropy, 1984, May-1986, Jan., undated (Box 29)
      - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition grants received: Summaries, 1979-1989 (Box 29)
    - Fundraising: (Box 29)
      - 1986 (Box 29)
      - 1988, Sept.-1989, Sept. (Box 29)
      - Alternate fundraising, 1980-1987, May, undated (Box 30)
      - Correspondence, 1983, June-1987, Feb. (Box 30)
      - Current sources, budgets, 1984, July-1988, Dec., undated (Box 30)
      - Publication support requests (Box 30)
      - Tips, guides, 1981-1986, undated (Box 30)
      - Miscellaneous sources, 1985, Oct.-1986, Sept., undated (Box 30)
    - Reports, 1981-1982, undated (Box 30)
    - Taxes: (Box 30)
      - Columbus, Ohio city tax, 1984-1986 (Box 30)
      - District of Columbia, 1983-1985 (Box 30)
      - Internal Revenue Service: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition tax appeal, 1984 (Box 30)
      - Kentucky: (Box 30)
        - Lexington city tax, 1983-1985 (Box 30)
        - State taxes, 1982-1987 (Box 30)
        - Unemployment insurance, 1982-1985 (Box 30)
      - Ohio: (Box 30)
        - Corporate franchise tax, 1987 (Box 30)
        - Employer's quarterly federal tax return, 1983-1986 (Box 30)
        - State tax, 1983-1986 (Box 30)
        - Unemployment, 1983-1985 (Box 30)
        - Worker's Compensation, 1983-1986 (Box 30)
      - Tax deposit, 1983-1987 (Box 30)
      - Tax exempt status, 1969-1984 (Box 30)
      - United States unemployment information, 1986 (Box 30)
      - West Virginia: (Box 30)
        - Excise and license, 1985-1986, undated (Box 30)
        - State tax, 1983-1988 (Box 30)
        - Unemployment insurance, 1981-1988 (Box 30)
        - Worker's compensation, 1981-1988 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous: (Box 30)
      - Economic Development Administration report, 1987-1989 (Box 30)
      - Federal unemployment, 1982-1984 (Box 30)
      - Letters acknowledging donations, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
      - Reserve fund, undated (Box 30)
- Writings Series, 1978-1989, undated (bulk 1984-1989) (Box 30)
  Correspondence, mailing lists, background material, and writings drafts relating to the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition publications. The bulk of the series concerns their newsletter Generations. Arranged in alphabetical order by publication.
  - Generations: (Box 30)
    - 1984-1986, (7 folders) (Box 30)
    - 1987-1989, (8 folders) (Box 30)
    - Advisory Committee meetings, 1986-1989 (Box 31)
    - Articles, 1985-1987, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Graphics, 1983-1986, undated, (3 folders) (Box 31)
    - Orders, 1989 (Box 31)
    - Reader survey, 1988 (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous: (Box 31)
      - 1986-1989, (3 folders) (Box 31)
      - Articles, 1980-1988, (2 folders) (Box 31)
      - Clippings, 1984-1987, undated (Box 31)
  - Southern Women brochure, 1982 (Box 32)
  - Working for Economic Justice Directory: (Box 32)
    - undated (Box 32)
    - Background material, 1987-1988, (4 folders) (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 32)
    - Hardcopy layout, undated (Box 32)
    - Letters-- Mary Ann Taylor, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Mailing list, 1988, undated, (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - Work plan, 1988-1989 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous: (Box 32)
    - 1978-1986, undated, (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - Drafts: (Box 32)
      - undated (Box 32)
      - Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 32)
- Personnel Files Series, 1981-1990, undated (bulk 1985-1990) (Box 32)
  Letters, time sheets, performance evaluations, and resumes chiefly relating to specific or prospective Southeast Women's Employment Coalition employees. Subdivided into three subseries. The first subseries, Employee Records, is arranged alphabetically by the employees' last name. The second subseries, Staff Recruitment, concerns recruitment activities for particular positions and is arranged alphabetically by the title of the position being recruited. The third subseries, Miscellaneous, contains a variety of personnel papers and is arranged in chronological order and by topic. This series is Restricted.
  - Employee Records Subseries (Box 32)
    - Alexander, Alice J., 1984 (Box 32)
    - Ashe, Bridin, 1988-1989 (Box 32)
    - Ayers, Shirley, 1983-1989, (3 folders) (Box 32)
    - Bacom, Mary J., 1986 (Box 32)
    - Bonner, Susan, 1985-1989 (Box 32)
    - Brown, Cynthia, 1985-1989 (Box 33)
    - Bush, Laura, 1983-1984 (Box 33)
    - Byrd, Norma Jeanne, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Care, Dolores, 1981-1982 (Box 33)
    - Conway, Glenda, 1982-1984 (Box 33)
    - Copley, Janice, 1983-1984 (Box 33)
    - DeAngelis, Regina, 1986 (Box 33)
    - DuBose, T. Lucille, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Feliciano, Suzanne, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - First, Emily Enochs, 1984-1985 (Box 33)
    - Gardner, Tammy, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Gregg, Georgan, 1983-1984 (Box 33)
  - Employee Records Subseries (Box 33)
    - Grose, Glenda, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Guillebeaux, Jack, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Hayden-Whitley, Shirley, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Hayes, S. Lisa, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Hearn, Kerthy, undated (Box 33)
    - Hensley--See, Nunna, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Jenkins, Nawanta, 1987-1989 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Joyce, 1985-1986 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Katie M., 1984 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Wendy, 1981-1989, (4 folders) (Box 33)
    - Jones, Karen, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Josey, Arlene, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Lambert, Kathy, 1984-1985 (Box 33)
    - Lawson, Sallie E., 1982-1983 (Box 34)
    - LeSure, Deborah, 1984 (Box 34)
    - Lilly, Leslie, 1983-1987 (Box 34)
    - Long, Cynthia, 1981-1985 (Box 34)
    - Martin, Meredith A., 1983-1987 (Box 34)
    - Morton, Phyllis, 1986-1990, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Mullins, Karen, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Owasoyo, Philomena, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Pharr, Suzanne, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Pratt, Sara, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
    - Rivkin, Fran, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Rogers, Vickie Lewis, 1984 (Box 34)
    - Sales, Rosie E., 1986 (Box 34)
    - Smalls, Idell, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Smith, Barbara Ellen, 1982-1989, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Smith, Donna, 1983 (Box 34)
    - Smith, Margo T., 1989-1991 (Box 34)
    - Smith, Michal, 1986-1989 (Box 34)
    - Smith, Sheri, 1986-1987 (Box 34)
    - Sparr, Pamela, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
    - Stamper, Laura Ann, 1989, undated (Box 34)
    - Tatum, Patricia, 1989 (Box 34)
    - Taylor, Barbara, 1983-1984 (Box 34)
    - Taylor, Mary Ann, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Thompson, Janine, 1984-1985 (Box 34)
    - Thompson, Richelle E., 1984-1985, undated (Box 34)
    - Wallace, Angelia E., 1984 (Box 34)
    - Williams, Lynora, 1984-1989 (Box 34)
    - Wilson, Donna, 1983-1984 (Box 34)
    - Wilson, Elizabeth A., undated (Box 34)
  - Staff Recruitment Subseries (Box 34)
    - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: (Box 34)
      - Board: (Box 34)
        - 1985-1990 (Box 34)
        - Buck, Ruby, 1985-1986 (Box 34)
        - Burnett, Carol, 1985-1986, undated (Box 34)
        - Davis, Portia, 1986 (Box 34)
        - Herrerra, Maria, 1986 (Box 34)
        - Joseph, Anne, 1984-1986, undated (Box 34)
        - Quinn, Beverly, 1986, undated (Box 34)
        - Simmons, Margarita, 1985-1986, undated (Box 34)
        - Tucker, Cora, 1986, undated (Box 34)
      - Consultant, 1988 (Box 34)
      - Executive director, 1986-1990, (2 folders) (Box 34)
      - Executive director, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Intern, 1987-1988 (Box 35)
      - Tourism Director, 1988 (Box 35)
      - Women's Opportunity in Road Construction Director, 1985-1987, undated (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Subseries (Box 35)
    - 1983-1988, (3 folders) (Box 35)
    - Interviews and evaluations, 1985-1986, undated (Box 35)
- General Files Series, 1967-1989, undated (bulk 1983-1987) (Box 35)
  Correspondence, reports, mailing lists, meeting notes, legal papers, and clippings. Arranged in alphabetical order by topic.
  - Abstracts, 1985-1987 (Box 35)
  - Aid to Families with Dependent Children: Self-Employment Pilot Project, 1987 (Box 35)
  - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1983 (Box 35)
  - American Association for Affirmative Action: Annual conference, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Apprenticeship and nontraditional employment for women, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Blue Collar Women, 1981-1985, (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Bringing Sister Home: The Fight for Job Equity in Appalachia, by Leslie Lilly, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Capital punishment, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Carl Perkins Vocational Education Act, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Civil rights: (Box 35)
    - 1983-1987 (Box 35)
    - Clippings: 1983-1987 (Box 35)
  - Clippings: Dec. 11 press conference, 1985-1986 (Box 35)
  - Coal Employment Project, 1984-1986 (Box 35)
  - Coalition building, undated (Box 35)
  - Committee on Environment and Public Works: United States Senate, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Comparable worth, pay equity, 1985-1987 (Box 35)
  - Concensus decision making, 1976-1987 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 35)
  - Cost of living, 1983 (Box 35)
  - Council on Foundations: Notes and meetings, 1984-1986 (Box 35)
  - Department of Education meeting: Ohio, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Economic development, 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - Economic Development Administration's National Technical Assistance Program, 1987 (Box 35)
  - Economic exposé, 1983 (Box 35)
  - Economic project: Mini proposal, 1983 (Box 35)
  - Economics Research Project, 1983-1984 (Box 35)
  - Employee contracts, undated (Box 35)
  - Employment eligibility verification, 1988 (Box 35)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1986 (Box 35)
  - Evaluation process, 1988 (Box 35)
  - Financial planning workshop, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Fiscal management information, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Georgia Women's Political Caucus, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Gund proposal, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Heritage Foundation: Working Women, 1983 (Box 35)
  - Highlander: Women's oral work histories, 1985-1986 (Box 35)
  - Highway contractor investigation, 1980-1983, (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Highway jobs, undated (Box 36)
  - Highway suit, 1980-1982 (Box 36)
  - Highways: Budget, 1983-1987, (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Highways: (Box 36)
    - Litigation: Meeting notes, 1983 (Box 36)
    - Lobbying efforts: (Box 36)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 36)
      - Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 36)
      - Project: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, 1980 (Box 36)
      - Proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 36)
      - Strategy meeting, 1980-1983 (Box 36)
  - Homophobia, 1986 (Box 36)
  - Immigrants in the south, 1986 (Box 36)
  - Institute for New Communications, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Insurance claims: Aetna, 1983-1984 (Box 36)
  - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility, 1985 (Box 36)
  - International Leadership Project, 1981-1983 (Box 36)
  - International networking, 1982 (Box 36)
  - Interview questions, undated (Box 36)
  - Inventory list, 1987 (Box 36)
  - Job descriptions, undated (Box 36)
  - Job Training Partnership Act, 1982-1983 (Box 36)
  - Kansas State University Action Agenda for Postsecondary Rural Education, 1986 (Box 36)
  - Kentucky: (Box 36)
    - Community Resource Center Workshop: Developing Organizing Skills, 1983, Apr. (Box 36)
    - Foundations, 1981 (Box 36)
    - Humanities proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 36)
    - Job Training Coordinating Council, 1982-1983 (Box 36)
    - Tomorrow Project, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Leadership: Management team meeting notes, 1982 (Box 36)
  - Lobbying, 1985 (Box 36)
  - Mail log, 1981-1983 (Box 36)
  - Mailing lists (Box 36)
    - 1981-1985, undated (Box 36)
    - Foundation women, undated (Box 36)
  - Management information, 1983-1986 (Box 36)
  - Meetings: (Box 36)
    - Atlanta Southern Dollar Campaign, 1985 (Box 36)
    - Economics project, 1984 (Box 36)
    - New World Presentation, 1984 (Box 37)
    - Organizing Committee notes, 1981, Mar.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: (Box 37)
      - Administrative committee meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 37)
      - Board/Staff meeting materials, 1985 (Box 37)
      - Board/Staff notes, 1981-1987, (16 folders) (Box 37)
      - Staff program planning, Shakertown, 1985 (Box 37)
      - Staff work on program development, 1985 (Box 37)
    - United States Department of Transportation, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Wingspread: Women's Economic Development, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Women and economic development, 1985 (Box 38)
    - Women in foundations, 1986 (Box 38)
    - Women's Opportunity in Road Construction Project, 1985 (Box 38)
    - Women's Technical Assistance Project: (Box 38)
      - Fundraising, 1986, Nov. (Box 38)
      - Planning Committee, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous: (Box 38)
      - Eisenberg, Pablo (notes), 1984 (Box 38)
      - Fillmore, Mary (notes), 1986 (Box 38)
      - Gillispie, Jack (notes), undated (Box 38)
      - Hensley, Jerry (notes), 1986 (Box 38)
      - Leeda/New York, 1984 (Box 38)
      - Management plan, 1985-1986 (Box 38)
      - Management team notes, 1983-1985 (Box 38)
  - Midwest Academy, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Missouri decision, 1988 (Box 38)
  - Missouri law suit, 1983 (Box 38)
  - Monthly reports, 1981-1982 (Box 38)
  - Mujer a Mujer/Woman to Woman, 1988 (Box 38)
  - National Committee for Full Employment, 1985 (Box 38)
  - National Institute for Women of Color, 1984-1987 (Box 38)
  - National Press Conference: Women's Opportunity in Road Construction Project, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Newsletter plan, 1984 (Box 38)
  - North Carolina data, 1983 (Box 38)